RANDY PANOPIO

www.randypanopio.ca randypanopio@gmail.com (778) - 926 - 8693 Vancouver, B.C

A design oriented developer with a core focus on user experience. Coming from a diverse background with interests from film writing, cinematography, to history research and digital art, I try to bridge ideas and create touchpoints in all of the projects that I partake in.

Skills

Technical

Iterative Design Process User Research Methodology Conducting Playtests Test Driven Development Agile Experience

Toolkit

Unity (2D & 3D) 3D Modelling (Maya) IK Animations Paper Prototyping Pixel Art & Animations Vector Graphics Shader Graphs

Development

C#, JS, TypeScript, Java, PHP XML, JSON, MySQL Web Frameworks (Angular, AngularJS, Grunt, jQuery) Git, GitHub, Unity Collaborate

Design

Adobe Suite (PS, AE, PR, XD, AI) User Experience Design Interface Design Creative Writing

Education

Simon Fraser University

Interactive Arts and Technology (SIAT), Bachelor of Science -Concentration of Interactive Systems

July 2021

Work Experience

Under the GUI Academy Inc. **Programming Instructor - Contractor**

Richmond, B.C **Dec 2020 - June 2021**

- Introduced concepts regarding programming foundations, web development, and game design to children with various levels of skill
- Taught children ages 7 16 concepts of programming through a hands on Unity project during weekly online class sessions

Safe Software Inc. Front-End Web Developer - Internship

Surrey, B.C **May 2018 - Dec 2018**

- Collaborated with a team of developers working on a core feature (Automations), on an enterprise web application used by over 10,000 organizations across the world
- Acted as a front-end developer and interface designer, maintaining and building web interface s for a suite of enterprise GIS management tools
- Worked in a test-driven development and agile workplace, building upon a hybrid Angular/AngularJS framework while maintaining unit tests with Jasmine and Karma testing suite

Projects

The Timeless Recurrence of Kagai **Dungeon Crawler - Unity**

Solo Project **Aug 2020 - Present**

- Designed and built various game systems such as the combat system, character AI, item systems, and level systems using Unity tools and internal tools
- Designed and refined game systems by applying research methodology and feedback integration from continuous playtesting sessions
- Built various internal gameplay design tools, including procedural content, and item management, allowing for effortless and rapid prototyping

Frigid - Glacial Path to the South Narrative Visual Novel - Web

School Project Feb 2019 - Apr 2019

- Integrated and extending a visual novel library through JS, and implementing the resource systems and gameplay scenarios while working alongside with an artist
- Worked as the creative writer and visual director of the project, adding 15 unique locations, 12 story branches, and over 100 lines of dialogue

Gallium Chalice Adventure Detective Game - Unity

School Game Jam Project

- Led a team of 4 in a month-long game project, where I managed our team from initial design, prototyping, implementation, playtesting and refinement process
- Programmed the core gameplay systems, including the dialogue system, player controls, and scene management